Good night.
Glad you could make it.
We were at the head of the gang at the festival.
He told me he liked me.
To all the Tokisei
Wrap your hearts, rappers!
We are super excited hypnosis!
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching.
Not a moment too soon Hadi Red patch
Thank you very much.
Yes, one time, Bank.
Can I go a little further forward, Min-chan?
Yes, ma'am.
Good evening.
Thank you very much.
Isn't that Mr. Otani of all people?
Etto-chan!
We've had about two rehearsals today.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll do my best.
Here's today's menu.
Do you have any Everoncino? What's this? Is it a choice?
It's my first meal. It's our first meal.
What? Look, it's water, Yokoyuri-kun.
Yokoyuri-kun.
You don't know how many you'll be.
You and Seishun are making me nervous.
Oh, no.
Are you okay?
I want some of this!
Looks delicious.
Figs.
Figs and...
Tangerine.
Definitely mandarin oranges.
With mandarin oranges
It's done!
I'll show you later.
A little more.
We're about to start the whole riff.
There are a lot of kids here today.
I'll try not to be nervous.
but I think my eyes might have been looking this way the whole time.
That's a lot.
I'm going to go now.
I got a pretty haircut.
Thank you.
Okay, we'll keep moving.
Yes, sir.
Yes, ma'am.Yes, sir.
I've always been so tense, no matter where I've been or what I've done.
Tomorrow's tomorrow's tomorrow's tomorrow's tomorrow's tomorrow's tomorrow's tomorrow's tomorrow's tomorrow's
Monday. Friday.
When this Monday is over...
I'll get a high-five from Momokura-san.
I'm so glad.
Good night.
What's that?
You can't get it?
Good! Good! Good!
What do we do?
What do you think they're gonna do?
I can't believe they're all covers.
Oh, my God, they're so good.
Wow! Amazing!
Ayame from Ukka asked me to have dinner with her.
Ayame from Ukka asked me if I wanted to have dinner with her.
I'm so happy.
asked me to take their picture.
I'm so happy!
Surprisingly, she didn't ask me to take her picture.
I wonder if she's your type.
I'm so glad!
Oh, and a cute memory of Mr. Ebitu.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 1 7, 18, 19, 201, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 1 7, 18, 19, 20
Grandma's self-pen
Jean of Butts Slip
Cute.
Yes, sir.
I'll have you all do the gah sound.
how long will it be?
Neta da da da da da
Thank you for watching.
Oh, it's okay.
YouTube and Teletext video
Eh! Hello!
I'm Kayo Date, Oharu's younger sister!
Oh, she's my sister, all of a sudden.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
I suddenly became a little sister
With my pinky finger
I'm Date Kayo, Oharu's pinky
Pinky?
Pinky when she sings
Just a little bit
Just a little?
Her voice is Monday and...
Oh, Monday.
You're so good!
Yay!
You have a great voice.
Thank you.Thank you.
And for the conversation.
And the conversation.
Which one was I talking about?
I learned.
I learned how to say it with my voice.
I learned how to do Noah's.
I learned.
Thank you.
It's on YouTube.
Do you remember that?
Yeah, I remember.
It comes from people.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He's a little too loud.
I loved that scene.
I rewatched it like 10 times.
I'm new to that ear moni.
I can't hear you at all.
I love that scene.
I've grown up.
She's grown up.
She's just a little kid.
She's a little shit.
From junior high school...
I didn't say "little shit".
I just said "kid.
Oh, no, no, no!Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Thump, thump, thump!
pound, pound, pound
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
It's okay.
You ready?
Yes, it's okay.
Is my face in the picture?
No.
I'm glad you're here.
Kaki and Ochi are here.
He's cute.
I like it.
I'm watching Captac after all.
I'm watching it too.
Thank you.
There's a lot of this going on.
They're really cute.
It's so cute.
I'm basically just kidding around.
A little bit.Just a minute.
Excited to see your smile
Excited to hear your voice
I can't wait to see your eyes
I'm so excited to see your smile
Excited to hear your voice
I can't wait to see your eyes
I'm so excited to see your smile
I feel like I'm overflowing
I'm alive
Ooh!
Oh!
Yeah!
Ooh!
It's so cute!
Oh my gosh, it moves like this!
Eater...
I can't compete at all.
They can't compete at all.Not competitive at all.
Cute.
She looks like your personality.
Amazing. Amazing.
You're so cute.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Look at him, look at him, look at him.
I'm tired.
Almost... Almost... Almost...
Who do you like?
Who likes who?
Stop, stop, stop.
Peter.
He's jumping so fast.
Oh, my God.
Cheer for me.
That's great.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
That's amazing.
Wow, Rin just did that.
I've got both.
I'm being a good girl.
I guess I'm getting a little greedy.
I have to get into it.I have to get into it.
What?
Grape sandwich?
There's strawberry, too.
Oh, wait.
Oh, no!
It's so cute!
Grapes.
How extravagant, Flaetz.
It really smells like apples.
It's amazing.
What kind of character are you?
I'm making up a role.
I don't know.
I don't know what to do.
What should I do?
Ladies and gentlemen, gathered at Yokohama Arena!
Today is
Stampler Idol Festival
New Autumn Song
have been harvested
Thank you to all the guests who came to the festival
sincerely
Thank you very much.
With Honoka Akimoto of Team Shirt
of the superficial Kesen Zenbei
The autumn duo of Ayaki SudaThe autumn duo of Ayaki Suda
Prior to the event
We would like to inform you of some precautions before the event.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
No assessments during the event.
No, you can't.
We'll have an archive of the delivery.
It's your paper after the show.
I wish I had that screen.
I loved it.
I knew it! I knew it! I knew it! I knew it!
You should talk to each other.
Yes, sir!
Follow the rules!
Have fun stamping traffic!
Let's have fun!
This is Honoka Akimoto of Team Shirt
and Ayaki Suda of Choshinkyoku
Yoshiho Kobayashi of Silche BES Junior High School
and Yuzuki Daikoku of Team Shirt.
Thank you very much!
Ha-ha-ha!
Cute!
Oh, it's so quirky!
Oh, I see you've got it.
Looks interesting!
I'm about to put on something really interesting.
It's going to be so much fun!It's going to be a lot of fun.
Yay!
Wow, he's so cute. He's so cute.
Your eyes are so big.
Hey, color contacts, color contacts.
You're wearing contacts.
I'm wearing contacts today.
You look delicious.
They do look good, don't they?
Did you bring it?
I didn't bring them.
I didn't bring it.
I'll take a picture.
I want to take a picture.
I want to take a TikTok picture.
I want to take pictures!
I'm starting today.
Oh, thank you.
Be careful.
Bye-bye.
Okay, bye.
The sea is so big, I can do it.
So pretty.
Poor little
Tangerines.
Are these oranges?
Maybe it's a tangerine. Wow.Maybe it's a tangerine. Oh, my God.
I took this before the show.
Oh, a baked sweet potato in the jar. The best part.
Aren't they cute?
It turned out pretty good.
We're going on stage now.
Well, I don't know when it's going to be performed, so...
I might be able to do the Christmas party while I'm working on this.
We'll have to be ready to go at any time.
Each of you will perform a new song.
We'll be performing "You and Youth.
I really wanted to sing it.
Yes, it's a song I've been wanting to sing.
I'm very, very happy to be able to do it.
I've done a lot of voice training.
Yeah, we all did.
We did voice training with the whole group.
We put a lot of effort into this song.
There are a lot of difficult parts.
So we'll do our best.
We'll do our best.
I'll do my best.
I'm sure everyone is waiting for it.
I'm sure they're waiting for you and your youth.
Yes, I'm going to do a medley at the end of the show.
I'm really looking forward to covering the songs there as well.
I'll do my best.
I'll do my best. I'll do my best.
It's starting. It's starting.
It's starting, it's starting, it's starting
It's starting.
No, not me.
It's our special.
That's my book, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
Yoo-hoo!
New.
This is the one from the tour.
This is YouTube.
Yoo-hoo!
Hey, you guys from the advertising department!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I messed up the lyrics at rehearsal.
Go to the side.
You know...
I know what you usually do.
Did he teach you?
It's gorgeous!
Gorgeous!
Gorgeous!Gorgeous!
Adorable, everyone.
They're adorable.
Congratulations.
Thank you. Thank you.
Send it, send it.
Send it.
Please.
Whenever Renri and I take pictures, we only wear casual spring clothes.
It's like a score sale.
That's right. It's hard to find the right time.
Yeah, it has to be.
Please do your best.
Do your best.
Cool, cool, cool.
Ladies and gentlemen, gathered here at Yokohama Arena.
Today, Stampler Idol Festival
Thank you very much for coming to the Autumn New Music Harvest Festival!
The early members of the team, Monoka Akimoto and
and the SUDARAKEN no Autumn duo from the Super Tokimeki Advertising Department
I would like to give you a reminder before the event.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Please refrain from eating and drinking in the auditorium and from disturbing other guests.
Eating and drinking are allowed in the lobby, but we ask for your cooperation in eating and drinking in silence.
When you say no, I feel like doing something naughty.
I was going to eat the package I just bought in Chinatown.
Ham-ham-ham-chow!
Vendor... the naughty, naughty, naughty ghost Jack-o-poo-chan...Vendor is a Karapeko naughty ghost Jack-o-Po-chan
Mark Mark Mark
No eating or drinking in the venue
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
The show is about to begin!
If you are in the lobby...
Please return to your seats.
Please follow the rules.
Let's make this a fun Stocktrapes!
This is Junko Akimoto
Junko Akimoto
and
Shumei and
of Ebisu Junior High School
Koko Kobayashi
and Yuzuki Daikoku of Team Orca.
Thank you very much.
Hey!
Hi!
That was fun.
No, no, no, no.
Thank you very much
You're so pre-cute.
Oh, I'm too tight.
It's pink.And it's pink.
This pink is too much.
All this pink.
Not this pink. This pink is too much.
If it's this color or this color of the clue...
If it's this color or this color in the clue...
I don't think it's pink.
But this one is too much
This one is too much
I think I've been told it's not pink
Oharu's pink is pretty high
Tough pink
Strong pink
But it's pretty.
Looks good with flowers.
No, but...
Oh, it's definitely red.
Yes, yes, yes.
My bad.
It's a gentle red.
It's not a strong red.
Maya's wearing this, right?
If Maya wore this, the design...
I can't wear the design.
Yes, you can.
Yes, please.
Let her wear it.
It's a little ahead of you.And that's going to come out a little bit first.
The one where you can only wear a few things.
That's not true.
I can't wear Haru pink.
There's a higher level.
I'm pretty sure they all have outfits.
They're missing an ear.
What? Come on, it's a secret.
I can't show it to you yet.
We're still human.
Still human.
A little bit.
A little bit like a cat.
This is a straight member.
It's true.
I'm always a little...
Oh, yeah.
This is...
Right here.
This is so hard!
Place-chan, place-chan!
Next, the "Super thrilling" advertising department
Propaganda Department
When I asked you to come out today...
I thought you all had something.I'm sure there are some of you out there who think you have something.
I'm sure there are some of you out there.
What is this?
That's right.
We're going to draw lots right here
We're going to draw lots.
We're going to draw lots to decide who will be in the show.
This is quite an ambitious collaboration.
Will you be changing for the show?
What number will you be?
Thank you very much.
Mr. Yokoyari.
I'm so happy.
Precious Yokoyu!
Cool style!
You both have twintails.
Composite, composite
Take it up a notch.
Take it up a notch, and have them take it up a notch.
I think it's going to be a cute memory.
I'm kind of doing this.
How is that, how is that, how is that done?
It's like... It's like... It's like...
Like this, like this, like this, like this.
It's not like this.
It's like this. Like this.
It's like this.
Oh, it's not like this?
And then, and then, and then...
We thought it was like this, too.
This is what it's always been.
This, more and more and more.
I mean, there's this guy who's been really good to us.
I'm trying to be so cute.
I'm not trying to help you.
It's not?
It's so, so, so amazing.
Anyone can be cute.
I knew that to get attention on TikTok, you need to be catchy.
The song just came out.
It's like a different song.
No, it's not.
It's the same waders under the same hat!
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It's the same song.
That's not true.
Well, then, we're about the same age as each other.
You noticed?
No, I don't.
Because we're good at something else.
He's cute.
Cute. Cute.
I love this place so much!
It's cute.
So cute.
I'm really into this place.
I'm trying to make this place a hit.
I'm already cute with everyone here.
So cute!
There it is.
I'm glad you told me about this.
I'm glad I noticed.
That was close.
Thank you.
You almost got me, didn't you?
Don't worry, it's cute.
It's just, you know, we're different.
You almost got me.
Watch out.
Please, please, please, please.
Please, please, please.
Oh, yes, thank you.
Hi. Hi.
Good morning. - Good morning.
Good morning. Good morning.
Good morning.
Oh, you want to take a TikTok?
I have to take a TikTok.
Oh, my God, you're so cute.Oh, nice and cute.
Oh, my goodness, you're adorable.
How do you like it?
Thank you for watching.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hoot and hoot.
Cute.
Cute, cute, cute.
Yeah!
Yay! Thank you!
Me too. Not at all.
Are you doing well?
I'm doing great.
You're so hot.
I'm hot.
It's so hot.
Yeah, I'm sure you are. He's super hot.
Compared to us, it must be very hot.
Surprisingly, the air flew away, too.
That's right.
It's love.
It's an adorable rider.
Are they different?
Oh, they're both different.
Here's YouTube and here's Mr. Claeser.
Wow.
Clairauther, on YouTube.
She's a great singer.He's a good singer.
Stop it!
He's so good.
He's younger than me.
In spite of appearances.
You're younger than me.
I can only see you as older.
Older.
Shoulder. Shoulders.
You can see his shoulders.
What's going on?
What happened?
December 2nd.
Oh, yeah.
Yes, I'll take one.
I can't see.
I can't see your face.
Your face is tiny.
Your face is cute.
Cute face.
It's cute.
Really.
Thank you.
Please.
You're cute.Cute.
No.
This girl.
Oh.
May I? We're... Totally backwards.
Totally backwards?
We sang one more time first.
We sang one more song.
It was very exciting.
The whole place was beautiful.
All kinds of colors.
Ms. Tokise's new song this time was like a coming-of-age song, wasn't it?
There is a zombie song this time.
Yes, zombies.
I'm looking forward to it.
I've been thinking how cute Tokise-san is.
I thought it was nice of her to wear such a cute outfit.
Really cute.
But on the other hand, I don't admire these outfits.
Not at all.
Not here?
I don't.
It has dignity.
Even if it's the same blue.
Yes, it is. It's totally different.
It's totally different.
They are different.Different strains.
Not so much.
Speaking of Sendai, I have a different opinion of beef tongue,
Fans stand with me.
They know I go to Sendai to eat beef tongue.
That's right. That's so true.
No, it's the same here. I saw it on your Instagram,
I saw on your Instagram that you came here just to eat beef tongue,
I was like, "Wow.
I was so surprised.
I was so happy.
I think I'll go see everyone.
I'm always there.
I'm always here.
I'll pick you up. I'll go to Sendai station.
I want to go. I really want to go.
I'd love to.
I want you to play with me.
Well, I'll eat as much as I want. Beef tongue.
Yes.
Next time,
Kanamin is going to eat beef tongue in Sendai,
With, with TOUKU-san.
What? I think I'll go there.
Oh, my God.
Anytime.
So, the exciting Stapler Fest has begun.
It has started. It has started.
We just did the raffle,
Basho-chan is now going to perform. Now.
What are you going to do when the next one comes?
What are you going to do? While we're filming,
I'll be in trouble,
Great, I'll let you know how thrilled I am,
Pounding.
It's kind of fun, isn't it?
I think.
What's the setlist for today's show?
Well, we'll be playing our usual favorites, plus a few new songs,
plus a new song,
Since this is a harvest festival, we have to perform a new song,
What new song will you perform this time?
Kimi to Seishun.
Here it comes.
It feels good.
It's a star. I'm imagining a star, like a star.
I'm so nervous.
Surprisingly.
I feel a little relieved.
The venue where the image is projected.
I'm so excited.
Amazing.
Also, "Queee! Yay! Like, "Yay!
I was so nervous.
There were a lot of fans there, Lots of fans were there,
Yes, I took this picture at the opening,
I was there for the first time in a thousand years,
And when Mr. Montori of Aperture was there,
The next group of people who came to the show were...,
Maybe the millennial group came next,
They fought against us,
They became the next group of people,
Oh, fighting the enemy.
It's Shiori, fighting the enemy.
They became our enemy,
I was so happy.
Thank you very much.
I don't know when it will happen,
I'll be ready for it,
I will do my best.
Thank you very much.
How many years?
Yes, it's been...
23 years?
21 years.
Twenty-three years.
Oh, sorry.
Sorry.
I was one year older.It was one up.
It was one down.
Thank you very much.
One more time.
I look forward to it.
Thank you very much.
It's my favorite.
I love the outrageous.
I thought the installations were so cute.
I love it.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
After this,
I understand.
After this?
It's okay.
Like me and No. 2.
Indian.
Cute.
Isn't she cute?
It is.
Gani-Ten-ten.Gani-ten-ten.
It's cute.
What do you mean?
It's not that cute.
It's cute.
Who's the second one?
They're all the rage.
Cute.
It's not good.
Really?
You're kidding?
It's a lie.
I just made it.
I'm proud of you.
Hey, wait a minute.
Please get mad at me already.
It's not good.
Please get angry.
Here we go again.
Oh, no.
He's really cute.
I feel like I've only been to dinner once, right?
That's right.
At that time, it was already time for me to go on my own.
We said let's go again, and we haven't gone at all.
Let's go.Let's go.
I'm a little busy.
No, we're both busy.
I'm busy.
Let's go.
Yes, let's go. Please do.
Please.
Yuna.
Cute.
It's fear, right?
It's onechan fear.
Good night.
It's been a long time.
It's a long time.
It's long.
Indeed.
Certainly.
Certainly.Certainly.
But firmly, a little.
I see.
Okay.
Good night.
I'd like to have it.
Yes.
Today, this.
Today, the same.
Same part.
Obake Shinmei.
You're facing Ko-chan, too, right?
It's Shinmei, isn't it?
Obake Shinmei.
Thank you.
I really do,
I really want to see your photo book.
I want to see it.
Let me see.
I'd love to see it.
Leave it.
It's cute.
Cute.Cute.
Cute.
Huh.
Thank you!
It's cute.
I don't know how to cut it, so I'll have to pull it for you.
You're kidding, right?
I can't see.
It's on Instagram,
I do it all over the place.
It's not cool. He's trying to tell us.
What's wrong with that?
It's nothing.
Thank you.
What's this?
It's a pouch,
The Madrese is going in,
If the Madeline goes in..,
The man in front of it,
Come to the store,
I was so cute,
I got pushed aside.I got pushed.
This madlace,
Come to the store,
I'm going to get hot.
Both times.
Oh, man.
Pervert,
I guess I'll say it again today.
Stop it.
Wow, thank you.
Thank you very much.
See you later.
I'm a showman,
More,
I won't be able to talk.
I'm checking with you.
Cute.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
I have to speak for the last time.
Oh, no.
It's close.
So close.
I can't do it.
Too close.Too close.
Too close.
No,
There was something I wanted to say today.
Totally, this,
I've decided that it would be nice to have it,
Oharu, isn't the way you're holding the microphone weird?
LOL.
Your pinky finger.
I'm not aware of anything at all.
It's totally weird.
Feeling,
I'm holding the microphone like this,
My pinky is like this.
So, why?
Where are you putting all your energy?
I don't know.
I can't hold it in the middle.
I'm going to pinch it with the purple,
Oharu, come to the middle.
I'll put it between you and the purple one.
I feel so embarrassed.
The two of them,
Surrounded by two people like that,
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
Laughing.
Berry, can you see me?Berry, are you seeing this?
LOL!
Laughing.
I don't know.
LOL.
LOL!
Yes!!!
Thank you.
Glad to hear it.
LOL!
LOL.
LOL!LOL!
LOL!
Shame on you, 말을
This Judge
Play it first
Play in Shimomura
me
But I'm doing it.
There are so many different kinds of music.
I think it's very rare to see such a beautiful in-lighting.
I'll do my best. You'll want to, won't you?
Well, here you go, Mr. Harrima.
I'll be right back.
I'm from the "Super Exciting Propaganda Department".
Oh, my...
All right, all you super thrilled promoters...
Please stand by.
And as I'm listening to you now.
I think we're on standby for the super-melting publicity department.
Oh, man.
You're good.
May I?
Next up is the "super-toki-meki" publicity department.
Stambhala Idol Festival Autumn New Song Harvest Festival
Stambala Idol Festival Autumn New Song Harvest FestivalStambala Idol Festival - Autumn Harvest Festival of New Songs
Thank you for watching!
I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I can't help it, I love you so much, I love you so much.
Let's have fun, everyone!
Cute, cute, cute, too cute
Cute, cute, cute I can't stop loving you
Hey, gentle nail fire, I have you all to myself
Cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute
Cute, cute, cute. Kiss all of them.
Cute. Cute. Cute.
Cute. Cute. You're a sin.
Dance with the whole audience!
Let's have fun!
And we here at Chotokisen...
We'll be performing here at Yokohama Arena on January 27th and 28th next year!
Please come see us live!
Come and see us!
We have been and will continue to give our all and perform to the best of our ability!
Please listen to the next song!
Thank you very much!
You and Youth
With you, I feel like any dream can come true
I chased after you and couldn't reach you
But I got it again
I wanted to make it come true, I wanted to make it come true
Without a moment's pause
We'll keep on fluttering in this heart
Don't stop, don't stop, don't stop Don't stop. Don't stop.
How can our eyes meet again?
I believe in uninterrupted time
It's me now, you and your youth
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, eight, nine, nine, ten, ten, ten, ten
Go Go To The Love Go Go To The Love
To The Love for the rest of my life
Go, go, go, to the love, go, to the love
Saisei To The Love, the strongest sense
Suki Suki Suki Suki Suki Suki Suki Suki Suki
Go Go To The Love
I have to make it come true
Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss
The sky to shine in the light Ispreka
If it seems like it's going to pop, I'll be delusional
Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss
Someday we'll be together, Paris
Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss
What did you think?
I love you.
Oh, my God!
It's just so cute!
It was fun, there were so many people.
Oh, my God, that's so cute!
Ohtani was so cute, I could stand on stage with Eugene.
I wish I could play with Inari, but...
Oh, that's one. I'm glad.
I got hot udon. I got the hot udon.
But the shichimi kara, oh, I got it. It smelled good.
It's funny that it smells so good.
I ate it.
Delicious.
Disney.
I love her.
Thank you.
She's cute.
Metal Ways has decided.
That shirt is the decision.
Oh, you've decided?
It's cute as it is.
Thank you very much.
Last metal.
Metal way, let's go!
Cute as it is.
Congratulations.
Because you checked me from a check that I'm used to doing.
Oh, did you show this the other day?
Yes.
Okay.
But today.
Oh, here we go again! Oh, here we go again!
Oh, I'm here now.
What's up?
Yes?
What is it?
It's this way! It's like...
It's hard.
What is it?
Ladies and gentlemen, the dance!
It's fun!
Always fun!
Yeah, I just wanted to thank you for your help earlier.
You've been a big help!
Okay, let's get started.
Let's get started!
Let's see!
Next, you're getting closer to the customers than you've ever been before.
You're getting pretty close after that. Closer to the audience.
I think they like you right now.
Six?
He's so cute.
She's really cute.
It's so sparkly.
It's been a really long time.It's been a really long time
Long time no see.
I'll be right here.
I know you're busy, but...
I know you're busy.
I'm busy by mistake.
You should be doing more numbers than you are. No, no, no, no, no.
Please like me again.
Don't be so rude. No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
After this, we'll go to the solo medley.
We'll be back on the main stage.
See you later.
No, no, no, don't make a move like that!
So cute!
See you later.
Umm...
Oh my God! I'm surrounded by cute cats.
So cute!
What do you say?
Micah and Mr. Micah.
Mr. Micah.
That's right.
He's so pre-cute.
This Thermo and Lilo...
Oh, my God.
Crikey!That's so cute!
Cute
Maine Alprecure
So cute!
I think the sides are falling down too.
I'm going to Iwate tomorrow to see the show.
Let's do it later, I'd love to ride with you.
There's three of them!
They all look like they're in the middle of their senior year.
Qui.
car
Me.
Cute!
The song is so cute!
Here I come.
I'm coming.
I've got to go.
Oh, my God.
Like a dark lottery.
You'll stay by my side the rest of your life, you swear? Sign here.
We're gonna have so many unforgettable memories together.
You're shy about it, but...
I'm searching my brain for what I like about you.
I'm searching in my brain for what I like about you.
You're too cute with your shy smile
Die-die-die-die!DIDY DIDY DIDY
We are going to have a solo live concert here in Yokohama on January 27th and 28th next year.
We are really excited about it,
We are really nervous, but we would like to give you a great performance,
Please come and see us.
Thank you very much for your time today.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
I want to take a group photo at 04.
Yes, so the staple festival is over.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you to everyone who came to see us, and thank you to everyone who supported us.
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much for watching the show.
I talked a lot today!
I talked a lot!
It's been a long time since I've seen you, and I'm so happy!
We also got to take pictures, and I think we had a day full of excitement.
Thank you to all the fans who joined us and made the event so much fun.
Thank you very much!
Five hours and 28 minutes.
Aren't you all tired?
I am not tired. I am not tired.
Eleven hours is amazing.
You performed some of my songs.
I took a picture of Kip, how did you guys like it?
How did you like it?
I thought I would perform this song again at the side walk and see the same scenery again.
We will continue to do our best for Yokobo, so please support us.
Thank you very much.
I can tell you now, the reason for my tears.
Whenever you're lost, remember it right away
So that you can smile when it rains.
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny sky, rainbow pools, making rainbow sounds
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny sky, tears fill my eyes
I'm wearing a rainbow dress
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
lalala, lalala, lalala, lalala, lalala, lalala, lalala, lalala, lalala, lalala
lalala...